this is why y'all lose this is why y'all lost let's be very clear this is why y'all lost
see i told y'all back then to have on y'all good listening ears and clearly they were not on tight
okay i never said not to vote for kamala harris but i did say that kamala harris will not win
the election because a majority of the country feels like the economy is doing badly she had
nothing in her part in her platform to actually address that problem period i said kamala harris
going to lose the election because she did not do an effective enough job of separating herself from
joe biden who was an extremely unpopular president who broke a lot of his campaign promises i never
said not to vote for kamala harris but i did say that she was going to lose the election because
a majority of the voters in the swing states that she needed to win said they wanted to see some kind
ceasefire an arms embargo in gaza um and so is it is it the fact that i said that not to vote for her
or did i say that people are not going to vote for her did i think a matter of fact that people are not
going to vote for her because she is not a good candidate and there is not a good platform
good listening are they on is it is it on i don't think so and this is a part of the problem
because if we're being so for real if they would have had a primary process maybe just maybe they
would have had a better chance of having a winning candidate let's be real if they actually cared
about the about the democratic structure of this country and of what it's supposed to be then maybe
just maybe they would have listened to what their voters were saying let's be real and let's not
forget about the fact that while joe biden was sitting up there in that white house there were
protesters all across the country on college campuses getting their asses whooped by the police
and by the military what the fuck is the difference you let me know all right
so